AHMED OUMER

Software Engineer

**** +251-927-970-190

@ ahmedinoumer13@gmail.com

AddisAbaba, Ethiopia

SUMMARY

Summary:

I am a highly motivated and detail-oriented professional with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Engineering and over 4 years of experience in software development. My expertise lies in PHP and JavaScript, and I have a strong command of various web technologies and libraries. I have consistently delivered projects within deadlines and possess excellent communication and problem-solving abilities.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

BSc Degree In Software Engineering
 Wollo University

EXPERIENCE

04/2019 - 08/2019 •

WU

Insurance/course project

platform where insurance managment are up and running

- · build the backend using laravel framework
- · build the frontend using Bootstrap css framework

2021 - 08/2021

Kiot

institution security/thesis project

Entry/Exit Security

entry/exit security project for kombolcha institut of tchnology that will applicable on entry and exit getway

- · build the backend with laravel
- · buld frontend with boostatrp css framework

2022 - 03/2023

AddisAbaba

website danaScholars

managing and integrating muslim scholars data

- build the admin panel using phpfilament laravel admin package
- · improve the performance of the platform using different technologies
- · design the database
- · build the frontend with vue js
- · collaborate with team members to solve development errors and problems

2022 - 2023

remote short term projects

Remote

Upwork

a platform for freelances job

- · develope the projects using laravel and node js
- · automate the projects using different technologies
- · build the frontend using Bootstrap css framework, vue js , react

06/2022 - 08/2022

WU

Digital Magazine

wollo 2022 Student commite
digital magazine for 2022 KIOT students bach

- · build the admin panel using phpfilament laravel package
- · build the API for the mobile application

EXPERIENCE

08/2021 - 09/2021 •

website

AddisAbaba

OPRIFS Ethiopia

- · build the whole website from the ground using laravel framework and Bootstrap css template
- · build the admin panel using voyager admin panel

TECH SKILLS

PHP/Laravel JS/Vue.js Css/Tailwindcss Scripting and Automation MONGO MYSQL

ACHIEVEMENTS



Participating in the International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC)

Participated in the prestigious International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) Regional 2020 Competition and placed 5th among highly skilled competitors



Participated in online competitive programming competitions

Participated in such as CodeForces and Kattis, and solved various algorithmic problems

Powered by CY Enhancy